dunkest.com 2016-06-22

# Privacy - Dunkest

### Privacy Information

RCS Mediagroup S.p.A. and Webentually Srl, individual holders of personal data, put a lot of attention to the protection of personal data and care not only about giving you a wide offer of services but also to ensure your right to be self-informed.

What are your personal data we collect?

#### a) Navigation data

The information systems and technical/software procedures underlying the operation of this website acquire during their normal operation some personal data whose transmission is implicit in the functioning mechanism and the protocols in use on the Internet.

Each time the user logs onto this site and whenever he calls or requires a content, its access data are stored in our systems and potentially also by the data owners and third parties in charge of the personal data, in the form of linear of tabular data (in special log files), structured and / or unstructured.  
Each line of data storage is composed of information such as:

  * The website from which you have called our page (the “referral”);
  * Your IP address;
  * The date and time of the request or access;
  * The request fulfilled by your browser or other client, in the URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) form;
  * The technical code of the response obtained from the http server (error, success, etc.);
  * The amount of data transmitted;
  * IThe browser, its technical and functional characteristics and the operating system used.

This data will be used by the owner for the sole purpose of obtaining anonymous statistical information about the site to identify the favorite pages by users to provide more adequate content and to check the correct functioning of the website. At the request of the authorities, data could be used to ascertain responsibilities in case of computer crimes against the site or its users.

#### b) Data supplied voluntarily by the user

In several places this site you have the opportunity to send personal data (eg. E-mail address, name, country, and other data). The sending of these data takes place on an optional, explicit and voluntary basis, and involves the acquisition of the email address of the sender, necessary to respond to requests, and acquisution of any other personal data for the purposes of service and those further allowed by you.

The personal information that you provide will be recorded and stored on electronic supports protected and treated with appropriate security measures also associating and integrating them with other databases.

The data and cookies you have received will be processed by RCS MediaGroup SpA and Webentually Srl exclusively with methods and procedures necessary to provide the services requested by you.  
The data will not be disclosed but may be disclosed where necessary to provide the service to the Companies of RCS MediaGroup and Webentually Srl, as well as to companies that perform on our behalf technical or organizational tasks, instrumental to the provision of the services required .  
Only with your express consent, the data may be used to perform statistical analysis, market research and delivery of commercial information on products and promotional initiatives of RCS MediaGroup SpA, Webentually Srl and / or other companies.  
Moreover, with your explicit consent, such data may be provided to other companies operating in publishing, finance, insurance automotive, consumer, humanitarian organizations and charities which will contact you as Holders of autonomous initiatives – the list is updated its disposal and can be obtained from data processor to set out below – for statistical analysis, market research and delivery of commercial information on products and promotions.  
After the registration required for the service requested, if you intend to request or use other services provided by the same company or different companies as indicated above (RCS MediaGroup SpA, Webentually Srl or their subsidiaries or affiliates) You can use credentials ( username / email / password) already used for the first recording.  
Where necessary you may be requested additional data, necessary for the provision of additional services required.  
At any time you can re-read the information and edit the consent previously provided, verify and / or change the status of active services and request additional services.

The provision of data is optional, except for those listed as mandatory for allowing access to the services offered. You have the right to know, at any time, what are your data and how they are used. You also have the right to update, supplement, correct or delete, to request blocking and object to their treatment. Recall that these rights are provided by Art.7 of the Italian Legislative Decree 196/2003.

The list of those responsible for the processing of data in this communication may be consulted at the legal office of RCS MediaGroup SpA in via A.Rizzoli, 8-20132 Milan and at the legal office of Webentually Srl Via G. Oberdan, 141 – 25128 Brescia; the exercise of rights under Art. 7 of the Italian Legislative Decree 196/03 can be exercised through a specific message by mail addressed to the same companies, or through the mail box dedicated: info@dunkest.com

In order to make it as comfortable as possible your visit to our website, and for the presentation of our range of products we use cookies. These are small aggregates of text recorded locally in the cache of your browser, and then into your computer.  
By using the cookie you can be recorded in a semi-permanent information about your preferences and other technical data that allow easier navigation and greater ease of use and effectiveness of the site. For example, cookies may be used to determine whether there has been any contact between your computer and our website to highlight the news or keep the information “login”. At your warranty, it is identified only the cookie stored on your computer.

#### Types of Cookies

This site makes use of four different types of cookies:

#### 1\. Technical Cookies

These cookies are necessary for the proper operation of the site. Navigation through the pages, shares our content, storage of your credentials to speed entry to the site and to maintain your preferences and credentials while browsing. Without these cookies we can not provide the services for which users access the site.

#### 2\. Statistical and performance indicator Cookies

These cookies allow us to know how visitors use the site, so to be able to evaluate and improve the performance and prioritize the production of content that best meet the information needs of our users. For example, let you know what pages are most and least popular. These cookies take into account, among other things, the number of visitors, time spent on the site by the average user and the mode of arrival of the website. In this way, we know what works well and what improvements to do, as well as ensure that the pages load quickly and the visualization is fine. All information gathered by these cookies is anonymous and not linked to personal information. In our sites we use the services of Google Analytics, Adobe Omniture, Chartbeat and Outbrain VisualRevenue to perform these functions.

#### 3\. Cookies for user profiling and targeting advertising

These cookies allow you to serve ads based on the users’ interests. They are also used to limit the number of views of the same ad and for evaluating the effectiveness of advertising campaigns.  
They are inserted by RCS MediaGroup and Webentually Srl through technical platforms of our advertising sales partners and contribute to our investment in Web sites, allowing us to adequately fund the maintenance of services and their technological evolution. They can also be used to show you relevant ads on other websites you visit.  
The cookie set can change at any moment because of the technical strategies of advertisers and their technical representatives. For this reason, instead of listing them, we denote the corresponding companies authorized to provide advertising on our sites.

#### 4\. Third parties functional Cookies

In this category fall both cookies delivered by partners of RCS Mediagroup SpA and Webentually Srl and known to them, and cookies provided by third parties not directly controlled by RCS or Webentually Srl.  
Cookies from our partners allow us to offer advanced features, as well as more information and personal functions. This includes the ability to share contents through social networks, access to services of video streaming and CDN networks on which we host our contents. These services are mainly provided by outside companies hired or integrated by RCS Mediagroup or Webentually Srl. If you have an account or if you use the services of such companies on other sites, they may be able to know that you visited our sites. Using data collected from these external operators through cookies is subject to their privacy policies and thus identify those cookies with the names of the respective entities. These include cookies registered by the major social networks that allow you to share the articles of our sites and publicly express the appreciation for our work.  
Cookies that do not come from partners of RCS Mediagroup or Webentually Srl, are conveyed without the control of RCS Mediagroup or Webentually Srl, by third parties who have the opportunity to intercept the user during his navigation even outside sites RCS and Webentually. These cookies, although functional, are not directly controlled by RCS or Webentually Srl, which therefore can not guarantee the use that third parties will make of the information collected.

#### Cookie management

In case you have doubts or concerns regarding the use of the cookie is always possible to intervene to prevent the setting and reading, such as changing the privacy settings within your browser in order to block certain types of cookies or using the tool that we provide below.

Since each browser – and often different versions of the same browser – also differ considerably from each other if you prefer to act independently through the preferences of your browser you can find detailed information on the steps required in the guide for your browser. For an overview of the mode of action for the most common browsers, you can visit:

<http://www.cookiepedia.co.uk/index.php?title=How_to_Manage_Cookies>

Advertising companies also allow you to give up receiving targeted ads, if desired. This does not prevent the setting of cookies, but stops the use and collection of data by some of these companies.

For more information and the possibility of waiver, visit http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/

To simplify the choices and in compliance with current legislation, RCS Mediagroup SpA and Webentually Srl provide a management tool for the selective activation and deactivation of cookies .  
Within the tool,, you can find listed all the cookies we consciously managed or hosted.

#### Acceptance and renunciation of cookies

By continuing the navigation on this site or by closing the banner information or clicking on any part of the page or by scrolling to highlight additional content, you accept the Cookie Policy of RCS Mediagroup SpA and Webentually Srl and cookies will be set and collected in the categories referred to in paragraph c). In case of rejection of cookies by abandonment of navigation, any cookies already registered locally in your browser will remain registered but there will no longer be read or used by RCS Mediagroup until a subsequent and eventual acceptance of the Policy. You will always have the ability to remove these cookies at any time through the procedures set out in the sites mentioned in the section “Manage Cookies” or using the tool provided by RCS MediaGroup SpA.

#### Acceptance and waiver of consent for the processing of data

The list of those responsible for the processing of personal data may be consulted at the legal office of RCS MediaGroup SpA at Via A. Rizzoli, 8 – 20132 Milan, or the legal office of Webentually Srl Via G.Oberdan 140-25128 Brescia ; the exercise of rights under Art. 7 of the Italian Legislative Decree 196/03 can be exercised through a specific message by mail addressed to the same companies, or through the email box dedicated: _info@dunkest.com_
